http://www.dominoes.com/privacy

$
Welcome visitor you can login or create an account.
Wish List (0)My AccountCheckout
0 item(s) - $0.00
Your shopping cart is empty!
Clubs
Have Questions?
Rules to all your favorite domino games
Looking for a great set of dominoes?
Custom Dominoes
Custom Cases
Still have questions?
Contact Us Here!
Clubs
Have Questions?
Rules to all your favorite domino games
Looking for a great set of dominoes?
Custom Dominoes
Custom Cases
Still have questions?
Contact Us Here!
- Double Six Engraved Wooden Dominoes
- Specialty Dominoes (PIP and Spinner)
- Licensed Dominoes
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (www.customdominoes.com). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Information Collection Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Continue
Categories
Stock Marble-like Dominoes
- Americana Series
- University Series Gift Set
- Texana Series
- University Series
- PIP Dominoes
- Specialty Dominoes (PIP and Spinner)
The American Domino Co.
